Okay, let's go, let's go.
よし、行ってきます、行ってきます
Wow...
うわ ぁ...
Looks like he'll do it
やるらしい
...
Home?
お うち?
My shoulder hurts...
肩が痛い...
Even if you turn your back...
腰をそらしても...
Have you gone?
行っちゃったの?
yeah?
ん?
You said you'd do just fine.
ちゃんと行くって言ったのね
Laugh.
笑いね
Because I'm gone.
行っちゃってるからね
Have you gone?
行っちゃったの?
One more time...
もう一回...
Raise your legs...
足を上げて...
This will go all the way in.
奥まで入るでしょ、これ
Look...
ほ ら...
Raw is good too...
生もいいんだけど...
It feels good, but...
気持ちいいんだけど...
But I can't...
でもできない...
What should I do...
どうしよう...
It's raw, just like this...
生だし、このまま...
Can I get you something?
何か出していい?
Why not?
なんでダメなの?
why?
なんで?
Just a little...
ちょっとだけ...
No...
ダメ...
That's fine...
いいじゃん...
it's okay...
大丈夫だよ...
scared?
怖い?
Just a little bit
ちょっとだけ
...
I haven't released it...
出 してないよ...
出してないもん...
I haven't put it out at all
全然出してない
...
Because I haven't released it...
出 してないからね...
It's kind of scary, isn't it?
なんか怖いでしょ?
Sorry, I took a step towards your breasts.
ごめんね、おっぱいに一歩かけちゃった
...
It's cracked again...
また ひびとんだね...
You're cute, housewife...
可愛いね、主婦ね...
I always wear clothes like this...
こんな感じの服、いつも...
It feels like this...
こんな 感じ...
This is how you came from home...
これで家から来てくれた...
Just as I requested...
俺が要求した通りに...
No panties or bra...
ノーパン・ノーブラで...
He came.
来てくれた
...
I was surprised, now.
び っくりしたね、今ね
...
I was walking around town...
街 歩いてた...
You're a pervert
変態だよ
...
I'm not even wearing underwear.
下 も履いてない
...
I can't see...
見 えない...
a...
あ...
It will open properly...
ちゃんと開いていく...
This is it...
これだ...
Skirt...
スカートの...
That's it...
あれだね...
material...
生地...
I'm not even wearing pants...
パンツも履いてない...
You're not wearing them.
履いてないね
...
Huh?
あれ?
Let me see...
ちょっと 見せて...
Behind...
後ろの...
Are you hungry?
お腹減った?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Is everything okay?
上大丈夫?
Yeah ...
うん ...
fault
あら
...
My liver came out again.
また 肝臓出ちゃったね
...
With both hands behind my back...
後 ろの両手でさ...
Open...
開いて...
here...
ここ...
Even as a dad?
パパッとしても?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Have you gone yet?
もう行っちゃった?
It's been a while...
久しぶりだ...
Yeah...
うん...
sorry
ごめん
...
Did you do a thorough investigation?
精 査したの?
That's terrible, the way you touch it
やばいな、触り方
...
Has it already come out?
もう 出ちゃった?
morning
早
stomach...
い...
I came out looking like that.
あんな目で出ちゃったよ
...
Wow, it's dripping
すごい 垂れてるね
...
Too erotic...
エ ロすぎて...
It's been a while...
ちょっと久々に...
Because we met...
会ったから...
Please forgive me...
許して...
Did you wash it?
洗った?
I washed it once...
一旦洗ったね...
Are you surprised?
びっくりしちゃった?
I just can't resist...
ちょっと我慢できなくてさ...
Why did you hide it?
なんで隠したの?
picture?
え?
Why did you hide it?
なんで隠したの?
Did you hide it?
隠したの?
Ah, now it's beautiful...
あ、綺麗になった...
It turned out beautiful...
綺麗になったね...
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
Now...
今さ...
You fired it with One Pero, right?
ワンペロで発射したよね?
It was a shock, wasn't it?
衝撃だったよね
...
It's scary...
怖 いじゃん...
I'm starting to get a little scared...
ちょっと 怖くなってきちゃったよ...
Lost my legs...
足抜けて...
Scary scary...
怖い怖い...
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
That's amazing
すごいね
...
amazing...
すごい...
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good
気持ちいい
...
Put your hands behind me...
後 ろに手ついて...
Take it out slowly...
ゆっくり出して...
Looks like it might leak a little...
ちょっと漏れそう...